Guide to the Henry Noble MacCracken Papers, 1907 - circa 1968
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES IV. STUDENTS, 1915-1950
  - Students, 1934-1938
    - R - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.9)
    - S - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.10)
    - T - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.11)
    - V - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.12)
    - W - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.13)
    - X, Y, Z - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.14)
  - Students, 1938 - 1950
    - Advisory System, 1943 -1945 (Folder 56.15)
    - Probation Letters to Parents (Folder 56.16)
    - General Academic Advisers (Folder 56.17)
    - American Student Union (Folder 56.18)
    - Athletic Association (Folder 56.19)
    - Baccalaureate (Folder 56.20)
    - Bulletin Boards (Folder 56.21)
    - Cap and Gown Committee (Folder 56.22)
    - Classical Society (Folder 56.23)
    - Committee to Investigate the Governance of V.C. (Folder 56.24)
    - Committee on Public Safety (Folder 56.25)
    - Founder's Day (Folder 56.26)
    - Freshmen Class (Folder 56.27)
    - Freshmen, 1949-1950 (Folder 56.28)
    - Freshmen - "Definition of Marks" (Folder 56.29)
    - Freshmen - Warning Letters (Folder 56.30)
    - Hall Plays (Folder 56.31)
    - International Club (Folder 56.32)
    - Newman Club (Folder 56.33)
    - Peace Council (Folder 56.34)
    - Political Association (Folder 56.35)
    - Political Association Conference (Folder 56.36)
    - Russian Club (Folder 56.37)
    - Reports Sent to Schools (Folder 56.38)
    - Reports Sent to Schools (Folder 56.39)
    - Reports Sent to Schools (Folder 56.40)
    - Reports Sent to Schools (Folder 56.41)
    - Sophomore Class (Folder 56.42)
    - Student Budgets (Folder 56.43)
    - Student Curriculum Committee (Folder 56.44)
    - Student Health Committee (Folder 56.45)
    - Student Schedule Committee (Folder 56.46)
    - Student Science Club (Folder 56.47)
    - Students Association (Folder 56.48)
    - Students' Building Chairman (Folder 56.49)
    - Student Welfare Committee (Folder 56.50)
    - Three-Year Plan (Folder 56.51)
    - Vassar Community Church (Folder 56.52)
    - Vassar Community Church - Conferences (Folder 56.53)
    - Vassar Community Church - Political Association Conference (Folder 56.54)
    - Vassar Outing Club (Folder 56.55)
    - A - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.56)
    - B - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.57)
    - C - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.58)
    - D - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.59)
    - E - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.60)
    - F - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.61)
    - G - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.62)
    - H - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.63)
    - I - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.64)
    - J - Students, Misc. (Folder 56.65)
    - K - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.1)
    - L - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.2)
    - M - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.3)
    - N - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.4)
    - O - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.5)
    - P - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.6)
    - R - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.7)
    - S - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.8)
    - T - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.9)
    - U, V - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.10)
    - W - Students, Misc. (Folder 57.11)
    - X, Y, Z, - Student, Misc. (Folder 57.12)
    - Student Records, 1947-1948 (Folder 57.13)
    - F - Student Records (Folder 57.14)
    - G - Student Records (Folder 57.15)
    - H -Student Records (Folder 57.16)
    - L - Student Records (Folder 57.17)
    - R - Student Records (Folder 57.18)
    - V -Student Records (Folder 57.19)
- SERIES V. ALUMNAE, 1915-1945
  - General
    - National Registration Office for Independent Schools, Honor Letters, etc. Alumnae, 1915-1920 (Folder 57.20)
  - Alumnae, 1915-1920
    - A - Alumnae (Folder 57.21)
    - B -Alumnae (Folder 57.22)
    - C - Alumnae (Folder 57.23)
    - D -Alumnae (Folder 57.24)
    - E - Alumnae (Folder 57.25)
    - F - Alumnae (Folder 57.26)
    - G -Alumnae (Folder 57.27)
    - H - Alumnae (Folder 57.28)
    - I - Alumnae (Folder 57.29)
    - J - Alumnae (Folder 57.30)
    - K - Alumnae (Folder 57.31)
    - L - Alumnae (Folder 57.32)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 57.33)
    - N - Alumnae (Folder 57.34)
    - P - Alumnae (Folder 57.35)
    - R - Alumnae (Folder 57.36)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 57.37)
    - T - Alumnae (Folder 57.38)
    - U - Alumnae (Folder 57.39)
    - V - Alumnae (Folder 57.40)
    - W - Alumnae (Folder 57.41)
    - Y - Alumnae (Folder 57.42)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 57.42a)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 57.43)
    - Endowment Committee - Alumnae (Folder 57.44)
    - Board of Directors' Meeting -Associate Alumnae, Aug, 1918 (Folder 57.45)
    - Brooklyn Alumnae (Folder 57.46)
    - California Alumnae (Folder 57.47)
    - Chicago Alumnae (Folder 57.48)
    - Cleveland Alumnae (Folder 57.49)
    - Indiana Alumnae (Folder 57.50)
    - New Haven Alumnae (Folder 57.51)
    - Philadelphia Alumnae (Folder 57.52)
    - Pittsburgh Alumnae (Folder 57.53)
    - Provisional Alumnae Council (Folder 57.54)
    - St. Louis Alumnae (Folder 57.55)
    - Alumnae Trustees - List of (Folder 57.56)
    - Alumnae in War Work (Folder 57.57)
    - Alumnae Council Committee Report (Folder 57.58)
    - Provisional Alumnae Council - Faculty Statistics (Folder 57.59)
    - Washington Alumnae (Folder 57.60)
    - Class of 1870 (Folder 57.61)
    - Class of 1886 (Folder 57.62)
    - Class of 1889 (Folder 57.63)
    - Class of 1896 (Folder 57.64)
    - Class of 1900 (Folder 57.65)
    - Class of 1901 (Folder 57.66)
    - Class of 1901 (Folder 57.67)
    - Class of 1906 (Folder 57.68)
    - Class of 1910 (Folder 57.69)
    - Class of 1911 (Folder 57.70)
    - Class of 1918 (Folder 57.71)
    - B - Invitations (Folder 57.72)
    - C - Invitations (Folder 57.73)
    - D - Invitations (Folder 57.74)
    - E - Invitations (Folder 57.75)
    - F - Invitations (Folder 57.76)
    - H - Invitations (Folder 57.77)
    - K - Invitations (Folder 57.78)
    - M - Invitations (Folder 58.1)
    - R - Invitations (Folder 58.2)
    - T - Invitations (Folder 58.3)
    - Aid Society (Folder 58.4)
    - Associate Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.5)
    - Atlanta Alumnae (Folder 58.6)
    - Binghamton Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.7)
    - Birmingham Alumnae (Folder 58.8)
    - Boston Alumnae (Folder 58.9)
    - Buffalo Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.10)
    - California Alumnae (Folder 58.11)
    - Charleston Alumnae (Folder 58.12)
    - Chicago Alumnae (Folder 58.13)
    - Cincinnati Alumnae (Folder 58.14)
    - Class of 1915 (Folder 58.15)
    - Class of 1913 (Folder 58.16)
    - Class of 1911 (Folder 58.17)
    - Class of 1900 (Folder 58.18)
    - Cleveland Alumnae - Invitations (Folder 58.19)
    - Detroit Alumnae (Folder 58.20)
    - Grand Rapids Alumnae (Folder 58.21)
    - Hartford Alumnae (Folder 58.22)
    - Indiana Alumnae (Folder 58.23)
    - Kansas City Alumnae (Folder 58.24)
    - Milwaukee Alumnae (Folder 58.25)
    - New Haven Alumnae (Folder 58.26)
    - New York Alumnae (Folder 58.27)
    - Northern New York Alumnae (Folder 58.28)
    - Omaha Alumnae (Folder 58.29)
    - Pacific Branch Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.30)
    - Philadelphia Alumnae (Folder 58.31)
    - Pittsburgh Alumnae (Folder 58.32)
    - Richmond Alumnae (Folder 58.33)
    - Southeastern Branch (Folder 58.34)
    - Springfield, Ohio Alumnae (Folder 58.35)
    - St. Louis Alumnae (Folder 58.36)
    - Twin City Alumnae - Minneapolis (Folder 58.37)
    - Washington Alumnae (Folder 58.38)
    - Western New York Alumnae (Folder 58.39)
  - Alumnae, 1920-1924
    - A - Alumnae (Folder 58.40)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 58.41)
    - C - Alumnae (Folder 58.42)
    - D - Alumnae (Folder 58.43)
    - E - Alumnae (Folder 58.44)
    - F - Alumnae (Folder 58.45)
    - G - Alumnae (Folder 58.46)
    - H - Alumnae (Folder 58.47)
    - I - Alumnae (Folder 58.48)
    - J - Alumnae (Folder 58.49)
    - K - Alumnae (Folder 58.50)
    - L - Alumnae (Folder 58.51)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 58.52)
    - N - Alumnae (Folder 58.53)
    - P - Alumnae (Folder 58.54)
    - R - Alumnae (Folder 58.55)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 58.56)
    - T - Alumnae (Folder 58.57)
    - U - Alumnae (Folder 58.58)
    - V -Alumnae (Folder 58.59)
    - W - Alumnae (Folder 58.60)
    - Y - Alumnae (Folder 58.61)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 58.62)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 58.63)
    - Alumnae in Post-Graduate Work (Folder 58.64)
    - Vassar Unit (Folder 58.65)
    - Vassar Club (Folder 58.66)
    - Class of 1900 (Folder 58.67)
    - Class of 1917 (Folder 58.68)
    - Class of 1918 (Folder 58.69)
    - Class of 1920 (Folder 58.70)
    - Class of 1921 (Folder 58.71)
    - Kansas City Alumnae (Folder 58.72)
    - A - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.73)
    - Akron Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.74)
    - Atlanta Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.75)
    - B - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.76)
    - Birmingham Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.77)
    - Boston Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.78)
    - Brooklyn Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.79)
    - C - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 58.80)
    - Chicago Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.1)
    - Cincinnati Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.2)
    - Cleveland Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.3)
    - Columbus Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.4)
    - Connecticut Valley Branch Invitations (Folder 59.5)
    - Des Moines Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.6)
    - Detroit Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.7)
    - E - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.8)
    - F - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.9)
    - H - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.10)
    - Indianapolis Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.11)
    - Little Rock Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.12)
    - Louisville Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.13)
    - M - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.14)
    - Memphis Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.15)
    - N - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.16)
    - New Haven Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.17)
    - New York Branch Invitations (Folder 59.18)
    - New York State Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.19)
    - P - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.20)
    - Rochester Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.21)
    - Richmond Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.22)
    - S - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.23)
    - St. Louis Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.24)
    - Sam Francisco Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.25)
    - Toledo Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.26)
    - W - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 59.27)
  - Alumnae, 1924 - 1927
    - Alumnae Miscellaneous (Folder 59.28)
    - B (Folder 59.29)
    - B (Folder 59.30)
    - C (Folder 59.31)
    - D (Folder 59.32)
    - E (Folder 59.33)
    - F (Folder 59.34)
    - G (Folder 59.35)
    - H (Folder 59.36)
    - J (Folder 59.37)
    - K (Folder 59.38)
    - L (Folder 59.39)
    - M (Folder 59.40)
    - M (Folder 59.41)
    - M (Folder 59.42)
    - N (Folder 59.43)
    - O (Folder 59.44)
    - P (Folder 59.45)
    - Q (Folder 59.46)
    - R (Folder 59.47)
    - S (Folder 59.48)
    - T (Folder 59.49)
    - V (Folder 59.50)
    - W (Folder 59.51)
    - W (Folder 59.52)
    - X, Y, and Z (Folder 59.53)
    - Class of 1897 (Folder 59.54)
    - Class of 1900 (Folder 59.55)
    - Class of 1908 (Folder 59.56)
    - Class of 1912 (Folder 59.57)
    - Class of 1917 (Folder 59.58)
    - Class of 1918 (Folder 59.59)
    - Class of 1919 (Folder 59.60)
    - Class of 1927 (Folder 59.61)
    - Class of 1929 (Folder 59.62)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.63)
    - Baltimore Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.64)
    - Boston Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.65)
    - Brooklyn Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.66)
    - California Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.67)
    - Chicago Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.68)
    - Cleveland Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.69)
    - Columbus Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.70)
    - Connecticut Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.71)
    - Louisiana Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.72)
    - Louisville Branch (Folder 59.73)
    - Michigan Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.74)
    - New York Branch - Alumnae Associate (Folder 59.75)
    - Philadelphia Branch - Alumnae Associate (Folder 59.76)
    - San Francisco Brach - Alumnae Association (Folder 59.77)
    - Vassar Club of Syracuse (Folder 59.78)
    - Vassar Club (Folder 59.79)
    - Washington Branch - Associate Alumnae (Folder 59.80)
    - Western New York (Folder 59.81)
  - Alumnae, 1927-1930
    - A - Alumnae (Folder 60.1)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 60.2)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 60.3)
    - C - Alumnae (Folder 60.4)
    - D - Alumnae (Folder 60.5)
    - E - Alumnae (Folder 60.6)
    - F - Alumnae (Folder 60.7)
    - G - Alumnae (Folder 60.8)
    - H - Alumnae (Folder 60.9)
    - J - Alumnae (Folder 60.10)
    - K - Alumnae (Folder 60.11)
    - L - Alumnae (Folder 60.12)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 60.13)
    - N - Alumnae (Folder 60.14)
    - O, P, and R - Alumnae (Folder 60.15)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 60.16)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 60.17)
    - T - Alumnae (Folder 60.18)
    - V, W - Alumnae (Folder 60.19)
    - X, Y, and Z - Alumnae (Folder 60.20)
    - Alumnae Announcements (Folder 60.21)
    - Alumnae Fund (Folder 60.22)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 60.23)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 60.24)
    - Conferences Alumnae (Folder 60.25)
    - "Listening In" - Alumnae (Folder 60.26)
    - Boston Chapter - A.A.V.C. (Folder 60.27)
    - Chicago Branch - A.A.V.C. (Folder 60.28)
    - Fall River Vassar Club (Folder 60.29)
    - Hartford Vassar Club (Folder 60.30)
    - New Haven Branch A.A.V.C. (Folder 60.31)
    - Northern New York Branch A.A.V.C. (Folder 60.32)
    - Philadelphia A.A.V.C. (Folder 60.33)
    - Providence A.A.V.C. (Folder 60.34)
    - Vassar Alumnae Association - Southern California (Folder 60.35)
    - Class of 1878 (Folder 60.36)
    - Class of 1880 (Folder 60.37)
    - Class of 1897 (Folder 60.38)
    - Class of 1900 (Folder 60.39)
    - Class of 1912 (Folder 60.40)
    - Class of 1918 (Folder 60.41)
    - Class of 1919 (Folder 60.42)
    - Class of 1926 (Folder 60.43)
    - Class of 1927 (Folder 60.44)
    - Euthenics Institute Alumnae (Folder 60.45)
  - Alumnae, 1930-1934
    - A - Alumnae (Folder 60.46)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 60.47)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 60.48)
    - C - Alumnae (Folder 60.49)
    - D - Alumnae (Folder 60.50)
    - E - Alumnae (Folder 60.51)
    - F - Alumnae (Folder 61.1)
    - G - Alumnae (Folder 61.2)
    - H - Alumnae (Folder 61.3)
    - I - Alumnae (Folder 61.4)
    - J - Alumnae (Folder 61.5)
    - K - Alumnae (Folder 61.6)
    - L - Alumnae (Folder 61.7)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 61.8)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 61.9)
    - N - Alumnae (Folder 61.10)
    - O - Alumnae (Folder 61.11)
    - P - Alumnae (Folder 61.12)
    - R - Alumnae (Folder 61.13)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 61.14)
    - T - Alumnae (Folder 61.15)
    - V - Alumnae (Folder 61.16)
    - W - Alumnae (Folder 61.17)
    - X, Y, and Z - Alumnae (Folder 61.18)
    - Alumnae Fund (Folder 61.19)
    - Classes (Folder 61.20)
    - Information (Folder 61.21)
    - Alumnae - Vassar Movie (Folder 61.22)
    - Georgine de Bobula Szalay (Folder 61.23)
    - Vassar Club (Folder 61.24)
    - Pittsburgh A.A.V.C. (Folder 61.25)
    - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 61.26)
    - Alumnae Invitations (Folder 61.27)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 61.28)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 61.29)
  - Alumnae, 1934-1938
    - Alumnae Letters (Folder 61.30)
    - A - Alumnae (Folder 61.31)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 61.32)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 61.33)
    - C - Alumnae (Folder 61.34)
    - D - Alumnae (Folder 61.35)
    - E - Alumnae (Folder 61.36)
    - F - Alumnae (Folder 61.37)
    - G - Alumnae (Folder 61.38)
    - H - Alumnae (Folder 61.39)
    - I - Alumnae (Folder 61.40)
    - J - Alumnae (Folder 61.41)
    - K - Alumnae (Folder 61.42)
    - L - Alumnae (Folder 61.43)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 61.44)
    - N - Alumnae (Folder 61.45)
    - O - Alumnae (Folder 61.46)
    - P - Alumnae (Folder 61.47)
    - Q - Alumnae (Folder 61.48)
    - R - Alumnae (Folder 61.49)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 62.1)
    - S - Alumnae (Folder 62.2)
    - T - Alumnae (Folder 62.3)
    - U - Alumnae (Folder 62.4)
    - V - Alumnae (Folder 62.5)
    - W - Alumnae (Folder 62.6)
    - X, Y, and Z - Alumnae (Folder 62.7)
    - Guggenheim Foundation -Re Muriel Rukeyser (Folder 62.8)
    - Christmas Letter to Alumnae Abroad (Folder 62.9)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 62.10)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 62.11)
    - Associate Alumnae (Folder 62.12)
    - Alumnae Honorary Award (Folder 62.13)
    - Alumnae Fund (Folder 62.14)
    - Class of 1878 (Folder 62.15)
    - Class of 1881 (Folder 62.16)
    - Class of 1887 (Folder 62.17)
    - Class of 1900 (Folder 62.18)
    - Class of 1925 (Folder 62.19)
    - Class of 1927 (Folder 62.20)
    - Cleveland Branch - A.A.V.C. (Folder 62.21)
    - Alumnae Invitations - Miscellaneous (Folder 62.22)
    - Alumnae Invitations - Miscellaneous (Folder 62.23)
    - St. Louis Meeting, Nov 1936 (Folder 62.24)
    - Indianapolis - A.A.V.C. (Folder 62.25)
    - Alumnae Invitations - Cleveland, Ohio, March 26, 1937 (Folder 62.27)
    - Western New York Branch (Folder 62.28)
    - Petition of Mabel P. Schmidt (Folder 62.29)
  - Alumnae, 1938-1945
    - Associate Alumnae, 9/1938-/1940 (Folder 62.30)
    - Associate Alumnae, 9/1938-/1940 (Folder 62.31)
    - Associate Alumnae, 1/1941-5/1942 (Folder 62.32)
    - Associate Alumnae, 1/1941-5/1942 (Folder 62.33)
    - Associate Alumnae, 6/1942-5/1944 (Folder 62.34)
    - Associate Alumnae, 6/1942-5/1944 (Folder 62.35)
    - Associate Alumnae, 7/1944-8/1945 (Folder 62.36)
    - Associate Alumnae, 7/1944-8/1945 (Folder 62.37)
    - A - Alumnae (Folder 62.38)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 62.39)
    - B - Alumnae (Folder 62.40)
    - C - Alumnae (Folder 62.41)
    - D - Alumnae (Folder 62.42)
    - E - Alumnae (Folder 62.43)
    - F - Alumnae (Folder 62.44)
    - G - Alumnae (Folder 62.45)
    - H - Alumnae (Folder 62.46)
    - I - Alumnae (Folder 62.47)
    - J - Alumnae (Folder 62.48)
    - K - Alumnae (Folder 62.49)
    - L - Alumnae (Folder 63.1)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 63.2)
    - M - Alumnae (Folder 63.3)
    - N - Alumnae (Folder 63.4)
    - O - Alumnae (Folder 63.5)
    - R - Alumnae (Folder 63.6)
    - R - Alumnae (Folder 63.7)
    - S - Alumnae (1) (Folder 63.8)
    - S - Alumnae (2) (Folder 63.9)
    - S - Alumnae (2) (Folder 63.10)
    - T - Alumnae (Folder 63.11)
    - U, V - Alumnae (Folder 63.12)
    - W - Alumnae (Folder 63.13)
    - W - Alumnae (Folder 63.14)
    - X, Y, and Z - Alumnae (Folder 63.15)
    - President MacCracken's Trip to Alumnae Branches, Apr 13-30, 1943 (Folder 63.16)
    - President MacCracken's Trip to Alumnae Branches, Apr 13-30, 1943 (Folder 63.17)
- SERIES VI. ACADEMIC LECTURES, 1931-1939
  - Invitations, Aug. 1931-1936; Lectures, 1932-1935; Preachers, 1933-1935
    - Invitations Accepted - A (Folder 63.18)
    - Invitations Accepted - B (Folder 63.19)
    - Invitations Accepted - C (Folder 63.20)
    - Invitations Accepted - D (Folder 63.21)
    - Invitations Accepted - E (Folder 63.22)
    - Invitations Accepted - F (Folder 63.23)
    - Invitations Accepted - G (Folder 63.24)
    - Invitations Accepted - H (Folder 63.25)
    - Invitations Accepted - I (Folder 63.26)
    - Invitations Accepted - K (Folder 63.27)
    - Invitations Accepted - L (Folder 63.28)
    - Invitations Accepted - M (Folder 63.29)
    - Invitations Accepted - O (Folder 63.30)
    - Invitations Accepted - P (Folder 63.31)
    - Invitations Accepted - R (Folder 63.32)
    - Invitations Accepted - S (Folder 63.33)
    - Invitations Accepted - T (Folder 63.34)
    - Invitations Accepted - U (Folder 63.35)
    - Invitations Accepted - W (Folder 63.36)
    - Invitations Declined - A (Folder 63.37)
    - Invitations Declined - B (Folder 63.38)
    - Invitations Declined - C (Folder 63.39)
    - Invitations Declined - D (Folder 63.40)
    - Invitations Declined - F (Folder 63.41)
    - Invitations Declined - H (Folder 63.42)
    - Invitations Declined - L (Folder 63.43)
    - Invitations Declined - M (Folder 63.44)
    - Invitations Declined - N (Folder 63.45)
    - Invitations Declined - O (Folder 63.46)
    - Invitations Declined - P (Folder 63.47)
    - Invitations Declined - S (Folder 63.48)
    - Invitations Declined - T (Folder 63.49)
    - Invitations Declined - U (Folder 63.50)
    - Invitations Declined - W (Folder 63.51)
    - Lectures Accepted, 1933-1934 (Folder 63.52)
    - Lectures Accepted, 1933-1934 (Folder 63.53)
    - Lecture Committee Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Folder 63.54)
    - Lecture Contracts, 1930-1934 (Folder 63.55)
    - Lecture Lists, 1933-1934 (Folder 63.56)
    - Lecture Regrets, 1933-1934 (Folder 63.57)
    - Lecture Regrets, 1933-1934 (Folder 63.58)
    - Lecture Committee, 1934-1935 (Folder 63.59)
    - Lecture Contracts, 1934-1935 (Folder 63.60)
    - Lecture Lists, 1934-1935 (Folder 63.61)
    - Lecture Acceptances, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.1)
    - Lecture Acceptances, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.2)
    - Lecture Regrets, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.3)
    - Lecture Regrets, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.4)
    - Preachers List, 1933-1934 (Folder 64.5)
    - Preachers List, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.6)
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1933-1934 (Folder 64.7)
    - Preacher Regrets, 1933-1934 (Folder 64.8)
    - Preacher Regrets, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.9)
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1934-1935 (Folder 64.10)
  - Lectures, 1936/1937 - 1937/1938
    - Film Showings, 1937 (Folder 64.11)
    - Lecture Lists, 1936/1937 (Folder 64.12)
    - Lecture Regrets, 1936/1937 (Folder 64.13)
    - Lecture Regrets, 1936/1937 (Folder 64.14)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Jaroslav Kose (Folder 64.15)
    - Lecture Regrets (1), 1937/1938 (Folder 64.16)
    - Lecture Regrets (2), 1937/1938 (Folder 64.17)
    - Lecture Approval Slips (Folder 64.18)
    - Lecture Acceptances, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.19)
    - Lecture Acceptances, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.20)
    - Lecture Committee, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.21)
    - Lecture Contracts, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.22)
    - Lecture Correspondence, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.23)
    - Lecture Lists, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.24)
    - Lectures - Folger Fund (Folder 64.25)
    - Lectures - Housing, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.26)
  - Preachers, 1935/1936 - 1938/1939
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1935/1936 (Folder 64.27)
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1935/1936 (Folder 64.28)
    - Preacher Regrets, 1935/1936 (Folder 64.29)
    - Preacher's List, 1935/1936 (Folder 64.30)
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1936/1937 (Folder 64.31)
    - Preacher's List, 1936/1937 (Folder 64.32)
    - Preacher Regrets, 1936/1937 (Folder 64.33)
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.34)
    - Preacher's List, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.35)
    - Preacher Regrets, 1937/1938 (Folder 64.36)
    - Preacher Acceptances, 1938/1939 (Folder 64.37)
    - Preacher Suggestions (Folder 64.38)
- SERIES VII. MISCELLANEOUS WITHIN VASSAR COLLEGE, 1914-1943
  - Miscellaneous within Vassar College, 1914-1920
    - Miscellaneous Publications and Programs, 1915-1933 (Folder 65.1)
    - Miscellaneous Publications and Programs, 1915-1933 (Folder 65.2)
    - Academic Freedom (Folder 65.3)
    - Activities (Folder 65.4)
    - Alma Mater Contest (Folder 65.5)
    - Admission (Folder 65.6)
    - Admission Requirements (1) (Folder 65.7)
    - Admission Requirements (2) (Folder 65.8)
    - Ambulance (Folder 65.9)
    - American Association for Labor Legislation (Folder 65.10)
    - American Council on Education (Folder 65.11)
    - American Council on Education (Folder 65.12)
    - American Birth Control League, Inc. (Folder 65.13)
    - American Glossary (Folder 65.14)
    - Anonymous Letters (Folder 65.15)
    - Arlington (Folder 65.16)
    - Association Membership (Folder 65.17)
    - Athletic Association (Folder 65.18)
    - Athletic Competition (Folder 65.19)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1914/1915 (Folder 65.20)
    - Baccalaureate Service, 1915/1916 (Folder 65.21)
    - Baccalaureate, 1917/1918 (Folder 65.22)